
# modified the DB Q to new dic from generated API
# https://opentdb.com/api_config.php

question_data = [
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "Vietnam's national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
                "correct_answer": "False",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "True"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "boolean",
                "difficulty": "easy",
                "category": "General Knowledge",
                "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
                "correct_answer": "True",
                "incorrect_answers": [
                    "False"
                ]
            }
]

